All $$ ain't good $$.
Highest 2 Lowest is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Spike Lee.
When a titan music mogul, widely known as having the "best ears in the business", is
targeted with a ransom plot, he is jammed up in a life-or-death moral dilemma.
David King, played by Denzel Washington.
Paul Christopher, played by Jeffrey Wright.
Pam King, played by Ilfenesh Hadera.
Kyle Christopher, played by Elijah Wright.
Trey King, played by Aubrey Joseph.
Yung Felon, played by A$AP Rocky.
Highest 2 Lowest is a 2025 American crime thriller film
directed by Spike Lee from a screenplay by Alan Fox.
It is an English-language remake of Akira Kurosawa's 1963 Japanese film High
and Low, itself based on Ed McBain's 1959 novel King's Ransom.
The film stars Denzel Washington, Jeffrey Wright, Ilfenesh Hadera, ASAP Rocky, John Douglas
Thompson, Dean Winters, LaChanze, Princess Nokia, and Ice Spice (in her film debut).
It is the fifth collaboration between Lee and Washington
and the first since Inside Man (2006).
Principal photography began in New York City in March 2024 and wrapped that May.
Highest 2 Lowest had its world premiere out of competition of the Cannes Film Festival on May 19, 2025, and was released
theatrically in the United States by A24 on August 15 before becoming available on Apple TV+ on September 5.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel
or book, ransom, remake, based on movie.
The tone is emotional and intense.